NICOLE SUE LYNN LEAW

Contact

% 0431 638 831

nicoleleaaw@amail.com



nicsleaw.github.io



Highett, 3190

LinkedIn

Skills

3D Practises - Autodesk Maya, Adobe Substance Painter, Mudbox, Unity

Adobe Suite - After Effects, Premiere Pro, Indesign, Photoshop

Video Editing - Adobe Suite, DaVinci Resolve

Website Design and Creation - HTML, CSS, JavaScript

UX and UI - Figma, Canva, Axure RP

Illustration and 2D Design -Clip Studio Paint, Photoshop

Public Speaking and Teaching - Presentation and demonstration of university level content and classes

Problem solving skills

Patience, conflict resolution

Summary

Highly motivated and compassionate multidisciplinary designer who seeks to learn new skills and further existing ones within a design field. 2 years of experience delivering educational university level tutorials for 3D practises (modelling and texturing for environments and characters), HTML, CSS and UX/UI design. Skills in digital animation and video editing using Adobe Suite, and passion for graphic design.

Offers great interpersonal and communication skills, demonstrated through collaboration with peers, and resolution and management of classroom and workplace conflicts. Skills in project management and teamwork as shown through leadership of final year university capstone project.

Work Experience

Research Assistant, Monash University

June 2024 → Present

Many Narratives Website Project

- Website design and UX/UI elements, as both a mockup in Figma, and created using HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- Realistic renders of Australia to represent geography and Aboriginal stories, using VUE and Maya
- Frequent collaboration with peers to manage deliverables Bike VR Project
- Creation of 3D assets, modelled and textured
- Representation of realism for a VR simulated bike ride, with constant consideration of optimisation and user experience

Sessional Teacher, Monash College

Feb 2024 → Present

Presentation of content and guidance for biweekly tutorial classes. Frequent communication between students and coworkers, to help and advise, and especially to motivate and inspire. Marking duties, to assess, and provide constructive feedback for student work.

- MCD4730 Foundations of 3D
- MCD4740 Web Fundamentals

Teaching Associate, Monash University

Feb 2023 → Present

Presentation of content and theory for weekly tutorial classes. Providing assistance and guidance in person and through emails and forums, to aid with comprehension of content, theory and practical use of software. Marking and assessing student work, providing thorough and actionable feedback.

Education

Bachelor of Design Major in Communication Design Monash University 2019 → 2023

Bachelor of Information Technology Major in Interactive Media Monash University 2019 → 2023

Referees

Rick Laird
Assistant Lecturer, Monash
University Clayton
0433 332 909
rick.laird@monash.edu

Rae Son Store Manager, Ray-Ban Chadstone 0478 788 143 raenn.son@rayban.com.au

- FIT1050 Web Fundamentals Creation of websites using HTML, CSS and JavaScript. Website design principles to aid in creation of mockups, wireframes, and with accessibility in mind.
- FIT1033 Foundations of 3D 3D modelling and texturing, optimised for animation and games. Demonstration of geometrical modelling and texturing in Maya and Substance Painter, lighting and rendering using Unity.
- FIT3146 Maker Lab In depth guidance and supervision of artefact creation, using microcontrollers and emerging tech.
 Providing support and direction for students to promote independent prototyping and refinement.
- FIT1073 Game Design Foundational theory about game design and narrative structure. Supervision and guidance of game prototypes and narrative writing.

Additional Experience

Retail/Optical Associate, Ray-Ban Chadstone Nov 2019 → July 2024

Senior staff member, providing excellent customer service with ir depth product and management knowledge. Optometry skills to best fit customer requirements and desires. Managerial tasks: quality control, stocktake, inventory management, and general organisation maintaining and merchandising product. Frequent customer management and relations.

Volunteer, Compass Community Care Canteen 2018 → 2019

Providing weekly meals, hospitality and a safe environment for those experiencing homelessness in Glen Eira Council. Involved in food handling, and meal preparation.